Jarmusch.
have you any idea how hard I work to stay in shape?
你知道我在多么努力地保持体形吗?
No, Sharon.
No,Sharon.
Have you any idea how much work I have to do today?
你知道我今天得干多少活儿吗?
See, on Mondays I go swimming.
你看, 星期一, 我去游泳.
On Tuesdays, I lift weights at the gym.
星期二, 我在健身房举重.
On Wednesdays....
星期三...
Let me guess. You enter triathlons.
让我猜猜. 你参加三项全能运动.
I run on Wednesdays.
我星期三跑步.
Thursday mornings, I go back to the gym.
星期四上午, 再去体操房.
And Fridays, I take a tennis lesson.
星期五, 我上网球课.
Congratulations.
祝贺你!
All to maintain my youthful figure.
这都是为了保持我的青春体形.
Now, let's look at your new menu.
现在,让我们看看你的新菜单.
Sharon...
Jarmusch, there's cream and butter all over this thing.
Jarmusch, 菜里全是奶油和黄油.
It's classic French cuisine.
那是经典的法国菜.
I like preparing it.
我喜欢做这个.
Most people like eating it.
大多数人喜欢吃.
Man cannot live on lowfat milk alone.
人不能仅靠低脂牛奶活着.
Pasta with triple cream sauce?
配三份奶油的意大利面?
Steak smothered in butter?
盖了一层黄油的牛排?
Potatoes with cheese?
土豆加奶酪?
Butter-cream chocolate?
黄油巧克力?
Excuse me.
打扰一下.
Jarmusch, a word when you get a moment, please.
Jarmusch, 在你有空的时侯,我可以跟你谈谈吗?